This is Wyatt, and today I sat down with Cyrus Shirazi, founder of Haven.
Haven is a modern tax accounting firm geared towards serving early stage businesses with
many customers in the crypto space and beyond. Cyrus has a deep background in and around startups
and built Haven to address a pain point he saw across high growth companies he's worked with.
In our discussion, we touch on how accounting is evolving in the backdrop of new technology,
serving the needs of startups, and working with companies in the crypto space.
Matt Walsh and Nick Carter are partners at Castle Island Ventures. All of these expressed by
them or the guests on this podcast are solely their opinions and do not reflect the opinions of
Castle Island Ventures. Guests and hosts may maintain positions in the assets discussed in
this podcast. You should not treat any opinion expressed by anyone on this podcast as a specific
inducement to make a particular investment or follow a particular strategy, but only as an
expression of their personal opinion. This podcast is for informational purposes only.
The Federal Government is stepping in to stabilize Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac,
the two mortgage giants that have been threatened by the housing crisis.
The Bank of England has pumped 75 billion pounds more to Britain's ailing economy
with a new round of quantitative easing. To print a couple trillion dollars and all of a sudden,
people start to worry. So out of this worry, we have something called the Bitcoin. Bitcoin.
Cyrus, thanks for coming on. Excited to chat. To kick off, I wanted to ask you what got you into
building Haven and what is Haven today? Thanks for having me. Great to be here.
So what got me into building Haven? From the age of 12, I knew I was going to build my own company.
Why? Because my dad worked in private equity for ballpark 15, 20 years,
quit his job, became a full-time entrepreneur, and I would literally run home from school every
day at that point and run up to his office and get to see firsthand him trying to take a company
from zero to one. All different shapes and sizes of companies. One was a pizza and salads business.
One was a chocolate company. The one ultimately became a baseball biomechanic center, which now
he's run for many, many years and has become super successful. But long story short is,
from that day onwards, I knew I was going to build my own company. And pretty much every stint
throughout my career was leading up until the point of launching something myself.
So during the few early stage companies after college, one was an SMS marketing company for
e-commerce brands. Another was an R&D tax credit company, which was part of the origination story
behind Haven. And then one was a crypto yield shop turned Neobank. And then for a short stint,
helped a good friend of mine raise a $15 to $20 million secondary fund. Ultimately,
secondary investing was purely transactional and there was no actual fulfillment or enterprise
value being created. I wanted the fulfillment of building something from scratch. And the
origination story from Haven's funny in the sense that if you looked at me and asked if I was going
to build something in the world of accounting and tax three, four, five years ago, I would have
laughed in your face. I did have the mainstream background of doing R&D credits, but even still
post that experience, I had no intention whatsoever of ever diving back into that space.
It just serendipitously happened. And so when I left my job at Nial, the crypto yield shop
turned Neobank, I basically set out to chat with as many entrepreneurs as I possibly could,
many of which were my friends. And a few of them early on, for whatever reason, as I was ideating
with them around different things within the world of financial services that I wanted to build,
they had never heard of the R&D credit. And I thought everyone had heard of it because
Main Street spent an enormous amount of money on LinkedIn ads and tagline was $50,000 and free
money for startups, but they hadn't heard of it. So I was lucky enough to help those few friends
claim their R&D credits, basically spun a C Corp up, got to 50, 60, 70 K and revenue pretty much
overnight. And that was the beginning of Haven, but completely separate from what we ultimately
became. I basically spun that up because I thought it was going to be like a nice little cash cow
and turn into something. But ultimately, that led to the origination of what we built today.
And fast forward a handful of months thereafter, after doing those R&D credits for those friends,
after talking like all the founders that were in my network and all the random founders that I
was lucky enough to meet, just kept hearing the same tagline, which is everyone hates their
accountant. And I was like, maybe there's something to do in this world. And then I had
something funny happen, which is some of the businesses that helped claim their R&D credits
asked if we could do other parts of the tax and accounting stack for them, the books and the taxes.
And I was like, all right, man, I think there's something here. Let's see what we can do. And
went all in and decided to build a boring old services company doing bookkeeping and taxes
and tax credits for startups. And fast forward to seven, eight months after that, we were like,
right around a million dollars in run rate revenue, profitable, building a great company,
had a rockstar team, I think somewhere around 10 or 12, including contractors, not just full-time
folks. Then fast forward to today, we raised a bit of cash, heavily invested in R&D and a lot
of the different things that we've built. And Haven's now well over $6 million in ARR slash
run rate revenue. And we serve well over 500 companies ranging from crypto startups to fintechs
to e-commerce brands to AI companies. And at the end of the day, we just love getting to serve
entrepreneurs and having a blast. I really liked that framework of go where there's scalability
and operational headache for companies. Because I think your past company, Meow, had a similar
framework to that of any startup knows they should be earning interest on their deposits. But
getting that up and running is just an additional to do. And it's similar. Haven,
you're capitalizing on the fact that this is something that people dread, but it's a need for
every company. 100%. At the end of the day, when I was thinking about what I wanted to build,
I was talking to someone who actually met over the weekend, but they were one of the
core members of the Alameda FTX team. And he basically said something which stood out to me,
which is that I only ever wanted to build a business where I was solving a hair on fire
problem. And when you think about someone hating their accountant, that's a hair on fire problem.
Because as Benjamin Franklin says, the only things that are constant in life are death,
taxes, and maybe something else, but definitely death and taxes. You need to do them every year.
And if you hate your accountant, you obviously don't trust them. And it's just a point of
problem that you really need someone who you can trust. So those words really stand
true in my mind. And I think that we're lucky enough to do something where we're actually
solving real problems for businesses. It's also one of those areas, I think if you're in a startup
even elsewhere, this can be true. There are certain areas that you spend a disproportionate amount
of time relative to the leverage that they create for your business or for your workflow.
And like you said, it's a hair on fire problem where that inevitably happens.
100%. I think accounting is just one of those things where in my personal opinion,
it's never going to be fully automatable by software.
Talk more about that. I want to hear about the platform offering and what level of automation
you can get to here. So I'll start with RevRec first, which is not automatable end to end
in like a future state, unless you have very, very, very basic subscription based revenue.
Why? Because all these enterprise contracts, everyone's got different terms. Sometimes there's
credits. Sometimes there's usage based billing. Sometimes there's addendums and side letters
to contracts, which throw wrenches into being able to automate things. What you would need to do is
parse a contract, which never looks the same. When OCR actually works today, it's parsing the
same type of document over and over and over and over again. And there's some repetitive component to
what they're doing, which gives it the knowledge to be able to accurately detect which components
need to be extracted. But when you're talking about like these enterprise contracts,
they're all different. And people go to Wilson, Sincini, and Cooley, and whoever else to draft
these super sophisticated agreements with their customers. And at the end of the day,
if you want to automate something, there needs to be some level pattern recognition.
There needs to be some level of consistency and repetitive nature to what data you're trying
to extract. But all of these pieces of information in these contracts are completely different.
So as a result of that, it's not fully automatable. And I personally believe it never will be,
unless enterprise companies agree to come together and standardize their contracts. But in no
world is that going to happen. Sales reps need the leverage to be able to have custom components
to contracts to win deals. It's always going to be a thing. But when you think about every other
component of accounting, that is what we believe is fully automatable. And when I talk about every
other component of accounting, I'm talking about anything and everything related to expenses.
So everything from transaction categorization to amortizing prepaid expenses, to adjusting
the service period for legal bills, to adjusting the service period for contractors, adjusting
the service period for vendors who are paid on net 30, net 90, net 60 terms. The reason being,
those pieces of documentation are all repetitive. You will see that this is on net 30. This is when
the invoice date was, that is when the service period was, and this is when we need to look at
two. When it comes to a prepaid expense, all you need is the invoice. Once you have the invoice,
you can parse it accordingly, understand if it's an annual agreement that was paid up front,
or if it's an annual agreement that was to be paid monthly. If it's to be paid monthly,
there's no accruals needed, it'll just automatically be recognized within the proper period.
Then when it comes to expenses and basic expense categorization for software vendors,
everyone from Google and others, you're getting bills for those during the period where the
services are rendered. So if you're using Google in June, you're going to get charged by Google in
June. So there's no adjustment that you need to make to when you're accounting for that expense.
And when you see Google once for one customer, you then know that it's probably going to be
software and it's probably going to be software for every other client period. It might be admin
software, and then there might be sales software like Salesforce, for example. But when you look
at someone's chart of accounts, you'll be able to see the granularity that they have within
their COA. So if you have two, three, four, five clients who are booking that expense as office
software, you know that's where it would belong in that new client chart of accounts when you're
categorizing those transactions. So that level of pattern recognition and reinforcement learning
when you're, quote unquote, fine tuning a model or training a model or providing data to a system
to then auto categorize transactions gives it enough information to be able to do that for every
business and like a go forward case. And that's where we've spent an enormous amount of time
when it comes to transaction categorization, when it comes to the automated detection of prepaid
expenses and their amortizations. And when it comes to ingesting invoices for contractors and
lawyers and other vendors for being paid after the service period has happened, because those
all have repetitive components, which we can identify and then be able to take action on in
the future. And so as things stand today at Haven, we've been able to automate right around 60 to
65% of the entire accounting process for a business on a monthly cadence. And then the Delta is
handled by our team. We believe that we'll probably be able to get close to like 75 to 80% in full
complete automation. But the other 20% is going to be the RevRec. And if you're a business who's a
basic subscription based software company, even if you have licenses and seats, it's pretty
automatable. You can basically just neck the stripe, you ingest all the data, you'll need to
break out fees and other maybe sales tax, etc. But when it comes to any business, what's called
enterprise level contracts, we're signing annual agreements or prepaid agreements or whatever it
is, there's so much granularity to those agreements, where it's really, really hard to
know when they actually used that service. So you might pay for something upfront for the year.
And let's say like it's Salesforce, for example, but the customer doesn't set up their Salesforce
instance until four months after the contract is started. In that instance, by a proper accrual
and in accordance with like GAAP accounting standards, you can't book any of that expense
until the service actually began to occur. So these nuances throw a lot of complexity into
fully automating accounting and to end, because there's something like bespoke and unique components
about businesses. And some of them don't even live in contracts. Some of them have to do with
business dynamics. You might sign up for a tool, but then you might not use it for like a few months.
And those automations or optimizations ultimately bring cost down for clients. That's the main
benefit there. Totally. And enable us to not only bring cost down, but then ultimately deliver books
faster. Are those immediately compatible with the workflows of a lot of the finance teams from
companies that you work with or their cases where their bookkeeping practices don't fully align with
the automation you guys are trying to bring to the table? So what I would say is our approach thus far
has predominantly been our ICP is on businesses who are employing, let's call it sub 250 employees.
And in those instances, they might have a head of finance, they might have a controller, they might
have an accountant, but they don't have a full fledged finance function yet. So they're more
amenable to changes and adjustments to their workflows if it means less work for them.
And when Haven comes into the equation, there's already an existing team. Our goal is to decrease
the amount of work that their team has to do that's mundane repetitive and laborious.
But when we're coming in in a situation where they don't have any finance or accounting function,
our goal is to automate everything end to end, whether that's with pure software,
our AutoCAD system, or by humans, the customer doesn't care. They just want it done end to end.
So to answer your question, it's really a context dependent situation in the more established
companies, especially because we're working with definitely like a lot of startups, they're more
progressive and amenable to adopting new things to make themselves more efficient and save them
time. And when it comes to the smaller companies, they don't care, they just want it done in the
most easy, stress free manner possible. That makes sense. How strong do you see the stranglehold
or grasp of traditional tax and bookkeeping firms being? I imagine startups feel pressure to work
with big names. So how did you guys start to win clients? And what does that look like today?
I've been lucky enough to build a bunch of amazing relationships across the venture
and startup ecosystem. And so when we pulled the trigger to get Haven off the ground and build the
business and a bunch of previous relationships who I was able to go and tap into to then become
early customers and refer and evangelists and adopters, which definitely like gave us a huge
leg up when it came to being able to build a name for ourselves and break into the ecosystem.
But in terms of this goes to a different thesis that I have, which is that some people think that
with the adoption of AI, legacy software is going to become more entrenched. I personally
disagree. Why? Because it's going to be easier to move data around far, far easier. So what that
means is doing the Klarna example of churning from Salesforce is purely an example of it being easier
to manipulate and take your data out of disparate systems and legacy systems and put it into your
own format to utilize in your own way. So when I think of legacy accounting firms, I think of them
akin to legacy software players, where they might have all of your data today, but it's far easier
to move this data than it once was. Even if you're going to use legacy example of a QuickBooks
desktop, that was a nightmare. It was impossible to change accountants. They had a data moat almost.
Literally. Because they had the historical records and it was difficult to access.
You had to physically go on site and collect hard drives and then that should someone else if you
want to migrate. Today, in the modern context of ERPs, pretty much everything is digitally
native. If you're migrating someone from one system of record to another, it's basically just a
data collection problem. And our approach to this has been very unique in the sense that unlike
other businesses who are trying to build new modern accounting systems, whether it's like a campfire
or a millet or even others, we're not trying to take customers away from their existing tools.
We're trying to integrate with their existing tools, but then automate all of the processes
involved in doing the work in accounting. So when you're working with Haven, you don't need to
get rid of your QuickBooks account. But if you're going to go work with one of these new ERPs,
you need to completely get rid of that and do a migration. That migration is going to take you six
months, which is years in startup time. You really don't have that luxury as a startup.
So our approach is to meet customers where they are, automate everything by routing all of the
data through our system and then into your accounting system, i.e. like a QuickBooks.
So I think that over time, the way that we win against legacy firms is enabling a frictionless
experience for our customers when it comes to onboarding. And if they know that they don't
have to undergo a six-month migration, all we have to do then is just build trust,
build trust with the stakeholders at our respective clients' companies. And that we've
done a great job of doing as a byproduct of doing an awesome job for all of our customers,
who then become a evangelist and testimonials and all of that.
Yeah, the composability piece makes a lot of sense. You just don't have the ability to churn
when you're trying to grow fast. We work with clients as they work with different tools.
Literally, some of them take six months. It's crazy. You see if it doesn't have the time to do
that. So a lot of these new ERPs are doing the migration for the client. At the end of the day,
the onus to some degree is going to fall on the client and it's not the best use of their time.
You guys are venture backed, correct? Yeah, we've raised close to like 3.6 million,
basically all of us still in the bank. So seedstrap, venture backed.
Do you get pushback that this is an unsexy business vertical or it's not really scalable or
something like that all the time? How do you deal with that or how do you think about it?
We lean into that component. So when people flag the unsexy components to our business,
the unscalable components to our business, the components that involve humans, we actually
push back. And I say that you just don't understand the business and people are going to be an
integral part of our company forever. Why? Because if you go back to the reverect thing
that I was talking about, it's not fully automatable. And the only way to provide a delightful
end to end experience for customers is to have a team to step in and handle and fill in the Delta.
If you think about a great financial institution, I'll use like Morgan Stanley as an example.
They've got a big time unscalable component to their business, which is wealth management.
A financial advisor can't manage 200, 300, 400, 500, a thousand clients.
There's only one of them. And we've all got needs. I have a FA at MS. I'm not that annoying yet,
but one day if I'm lucky enough to make a bunch of money, yeah, I'm going to be annoying and
take a bunch of this time. Morgan Stanley is what? Two, three hundred billion dollar company.
At the end of the day, to build a great financial institution, you need to have a great
services component to your business. If you're touching any of the components in financial
services that are more services than just finance. If you're touching more in the context of FinTech,
if you're touching more like thin versus tech, you need services. Savvy wealth is a great company
who is building like a new financial wealth management platform. They've got advisors on
their team. They just raised a hundred million dollars. We really, really lean into the services,
the software narratives, the AI services. And a lot of people have the opinion that, oh,
if you're AI services, you need to automate all of the service and then into software. No,
because who's going to manage the relationship at the end of the day? That's the most important part.
So in our vision, the relationship ultimately becomes managed by accountants,
and the work is basically all done in automated form with some level of human in the loop.
I think the services side of software gets completely unnoticed. And I used to follow
data software businesses, so like Bloomberg, CoStar, Gartner, and they do so much on the ground
data gathering because there's no other way to do it. And that's just human-based. And maybe that'll
change, but there's certain things you can't automate in terms of calling companies, pitch
book style, and asking for data. Think about scale AI. The only reason that these great LLM players
able to exist is because they have human-labeled data. The only way that they continue to get
better and better and better is with human-labeled data. So it's a flywheel that all grows on itself
that is all interconnected. And there's almost a fallacy because if there's not a human proprietary
element, anyone could do it. Period. At the end of the day, also financial services, part of the
moat long-term becomes the relationship you have with your customers and the density of your customers
and the success of your customers. And a lot of people make irrational decisions in the world.
People use HubSpot and Salesforce because they have a pre-existing relationship there.
Whether or not it's a logical decision, HubSpot is better, Salesforce is better, doesn't matter.
They end up using one of these tools because they have a relationship there,
which is just fascinating to put into that.
Switching gears a little bit, you guys work closely with crypto startups. You have crypto-based
clients. Yeah, we have a bunch. How are your workflows specific there? Or what do they look
like and how do you work with those firms? Our crypto clients, the workflows, when everything
is in fiat, is exactly the same. The crypto component of the business, we are able to automate by
partnering and working with different accounting tools like BitWave and Integral and CoinTracker,
CryptoTaxCalculator and a few others. And at the end of the day, all we need is ending balances
to take from all of their on-chain activity, whether it's ending balances for payroll,
which break out fees and taxes and withholdings and insurance. And then we create a journal entry
in their P&L balance sheet, cash flow statement to account for all of that.
The workflow involved in doing accounting for crypto-related businesses, honestly,
isn't that different from doing it for traditional fiat companies? I think our crypto clients
probably involve a little bit more work than the traditional fiat business because of the
on-chain component. But at the end of the day, we look at them as pretty much one in the same as
the traditional companies that we're working with. And we love working with crypto businesses.
We don't shy away from it at all. I've been in crypto for a long time. One of my co-founders
has as well, or I should say both of them. Some of our team has as well. We look at it as like a
not even challenge, it's an exciting opportunity to work with a bunch of amazing businesses. And
one of our customers is Ansible Labs, who's helping facilitate on-ramps and off-ramps.
Beam, sorry, apologies, I know you changed the name. So a bunch of awesome companies like that.
And I think crypto is back, whether it's a testament to the new administration or not.
I think the world is beginning to see far more of the use cases for crypto,
specifically when it comes to cross-border payments. In my opinion, it's one of the biggest
use cases. The founder of AirWallet, the other day, tweeted about how it's more expensive to
move crypto around the world when you're talking about off-ramping and fees stemming from that,
than it is to move fiat around the world. Because they built this network of partner banks across
many parts of the world, which has made the FX fees pretty negligible. But if you think about
all the bullshit involved in moving money around the world, and how slow it is when it comes to
FX, it's not even quantifiable how much more efficient it is to move money around the world
in the form of stables or in the form of crypto.
Just last steps, someone can subsidize the traditional FX payment on a temporary basis?
100%. One of our north stars at Haven is clicks to value. So how can you turn
every experience into one click? And there's no universe in which sending an international wire
or international payment is one click. It's just not fundamentally possible.
We were talking about this the other day. People will ask how stablecoins work or
really scrutinize that. And you also want to ask, how does a wire work? Can you explain to me how
a wire works? Literally. I think there's some validity to what he's saying in the context of
off-ramping and the fee stemming from that. Which Beam tries to solve, for example,
and a lot of its companies are trying to fix. My counter to him was that what happens when
you don't need to off-ramp and you can just transact anywhere in crypto, period.
When you're spending money on a card and you can just settle on the other end in stables or in
crypto, there's no off-ramp costs. It's literally just maybe the crypto synonymous version of
interchange if it were to ever exist. Do you work with companies that are taking on
Bitcoin balance sheet strategies? And does that impact your workflow with them?
We do. So we have a bunch of clients who hold Bitcoin on the balance sheet. I'm not of the
speed enough on the context of their unique circumstances to understand or know if they're
deploying a strategy to take advantage of cost discrepancies across different exchanges
with FanBank, McFreed, ultimately did in FTX. That I'm not sure about. But a bunch of clients
that have Bitcoin on the balance sheet specifically, it's a great store of value. But I'm not super,
super close to that part. But I'm sure they're doing some unique things.
Do you think that stablecoin workflows long-term will just make this entire job easier in terms of
having clear, on-chain accountability of money flows and hopefully simpler tracking of balances,
et cetera? Yes. If someone's able to build plaid for crypto.
What do you see that business model looking like? Because we've gotten some pitches,
but I'd like to hear where you see the white space there.
So basically, you can go in to a financial platform and connect any and all of your accounts,
wallets, everything in a manner that is then broken out and displayed in dollars.
Just a universal account, essentially. Universal account, 100% for sure. But basically,
everyone has so many different wallets, so many different exchanges that they use,
so many different taxes, et cetera. You basically need, and I know there's tools out there who do
this like crypto tax calculator and CoinTracker and others where you can connect and it'll show
all of the deficit credit, so on and so forth. But it's still in a semi-difficult to digest form
for accounting purposes. Why? Because there's no description or vendor name associated with these
transactions. So maybe this isn't like a plaid specific use case, but one of the reasons that
doing accounting in the context of fiat-related businesses is every transaction has a vendor
and a description. But when you're doing on-chain accounting, there's no vendor and description
associated with every single transaction. And so the reason I mentioned something like a plaid is
some sort of financial institution to aggregate all of the data and help label it.
Well, it sounds like someone on the data labeling side itself would be helpful, too.
It's almost like both sides of that coin would be helpful.
100%. Right now, the only people who know what wallets transactions are for is whoever owns
that wallet. Once we have vendor name and description associated with any and all crypto
related transactions, accounting will be 1,000 times easier and become far more akin to standard
fiat accounting. But until we're at that place, it's going to be far more difficult to do. But
I think one of the ways to do it is a company called Rain, for example, where you can basically
spend from any crypto wallet, they have all of the vendor data. So wherever you spend money on
that card, they know who you're spending it with. So they have the data to be able to label all of
those transactions. Basically, we need more institutions like that across different parts
of the crypto ecosystem to help with labeling transaction level data to make accounting easier
for these businesses. But to your point, Rain are expressly a crypto card payments company,
and they've taken on this responsibility of doing the labeling. But there's no one who said,
I'm just going to go and try and aggregate identity level data for the use of accounting
and general traceability to massively scale. That's a visit in itself, probably.
Yeah, I completely agree, especially because as we get this crypto inflection that we were both
talking about, for so long, people thought of the anonymity as a feature, not a bug.
And I think now, in a lot of cases, it's a bug, not a feature. And if you ask a large subset of
these stablecoin users, the anonymity is no longer something that people index on or care
that much about widely. They dislike it. They dislike it because it makes more work for them
later on. Exactly. They want all the benefits of crypto without the anonymous components because
they want to use it like fiat for the benefits that it has over fiat, instant payments, fewer
clicks to value, no bulk when it comes to currency deflation and all that stuff.
Yeah, if anyone wants to build a labeling business in the crypto space, they should reach out to us.
I love it. Yeah, that would be a great business. I would love to partner with them too.
Will you guys ever turn down potential clients in the crypto space or otherwise?
We've definitely turned down clients. We've actually fired clients as well. We've fired
clients and turned them down for more often than not being unreasonable. And when I say unreasonable,
what I mean is redlining a SMB 10K ACV contract and asking us to bring in legal resources to
help get the deal over the line. And it's going to cut drastically into our margins.
That just fundamentally doesn't make sense for our business. No offense to them whatsoever. But
it's just not a good use of our time or our resources. We're already paying for the cost
of acquiring the customer, whether it's through sale salaries or my salary or my co-founder
salary or marketing salaries or marketing spend, whatever it is. We've had some people
ask for some weird quote unquote favors, which is if I get paid in cash or via Venmo,
don't add it to my books. They immediately got fired.
That seems like a reasonable policy for you guys.
Totally. And then there's a handful of customers who we've worked with who just haven't operated
with what we would call mutual respect. And I think in the professional services world,
there's a lot of taking shit from customers because not everything is done via software.
There's humans and people make mistakes for sure. But at the end of the day, you have to operate with
a reasonable level of mutual respect. We're doing everything we can to make sure we do an amazing
job. And I like to think we do a 10X better job than all of the competition. You're more than welcome
to go explore working with someone else if you're not having a great experience with us.
And then you'll know what it means to have had a good experience with an accountant.
They're not the most proactive. They're not the most customer centric. They're not the most
responsive individuals. And I think that at the end of the day, we're trying to work with people
who want to work with us for the long term. And to double back to your question, who will we turn
down? We'll turn down people who want one-off engagements. If you want us to just handle
something where it's a cleanup of your transactions historically and then nothing gonna go forward,
cadence, we won't work with you. It just doesn't make sense for us. If you want us to just handle
your taxes one-off for one year, we won't work with you. It doesn't make sense for us.
We want to work with people for the next 100 years. So, who's ever willing to come up to the
table and take a crack at doing that and changing the future with us, we're here and we're ready
to go above and beyond for you. But everyone else, we're probably not the best fit for. And that's
totally okay. What advice would you give to early-stage companies as they're navigating these
decisions? When it comes to accounting specifically, first and foremost, find someone you trust.
Find someone who you believe is going to be there for you when you need them, who is going to
do everything by the book accurately, correctly, so on and so forth. Don't look for someone who's
going to try to help you solve and optimize all the gray areas of the tax code. At the end of the
day, you don't hear about the filthy, rich people, the super affluent, super successful people of our
generation spending their time trying to optimize every dollar from a tax standpoint. You want to
find someone who's going to do an amazing job, follow every letter of the law, and help you
save time and money in the process of it. If you are building a startup, your focus should be on
building the business. And you want to find someone who's going to make sure that you have every T,
every I cross when it comes to all the accounting and tax and compliance components of your business,
and just trust them to put it on autopilot. You don't want to find the strategist or the guru
who's going to help you save a few pennies here and there. At the end of the day, you're shooting
for like a billion, $10 billion, $100 billion outcome. And the few pennies that you save here
along the way, they're not going to make a breakthrough business. So you want to find someone
who is prepped, primed, and ready to help you scale for the next many, many years and who can
grow with you, who understands what it means to be like an early stage company and who's not going
to price gouge you or try to milk every dollar out of you from the early onset of the relationship
with them. Save advice. Well, appreciate it. We'll leave it there. And Cyrus, thanks for coming on.
Hopefully, you can join us again sometime. Thank you, sir. Appreciate you. Great to be here.
Thanks for listening to another episode of On the Brink with Castle Island. To find out more
about Castle Island, visit castleisland.vc. To listen to all of our podcast episodes,
please go to onthebrink-podcast.com or just click on the tab in our website. Thanks for listening.